Greetings, my friend. We are
all interested in the future,
for that is where you and I
are going to spend the
rest of our lives.
And remember my friend, future
events such as these will affect
you in the future.
You are interested in the
unknown, the mysterious, the unexplainable.
That is why you are here.
And now, for the first time,
we are bringing to you the full story of what
happened on that fateful day.
We are giving you all the evidence, based
only on the secret testimony
of the miserable souls who survived
this terrifying ordeal. The
incidents, the places,
my friend we cannot keep this a secret any longer.
Let us punish the guilty,
let us reward the innocent. My friend,
can your heart stand the shocking facts
about grave robbers
from outer space?
All of us on this earth, know that
there is a time to live,
and that there is a time to die,
yet death is always a shock
to those left behind.
It is even more of a shock, when death,
the proud brother, comes suddenly without warning.
Just at sundown, a small group,
gathered in silent prayer around
the newly-opened grave
of the beloved wife of an elderly man.
Sundown of the day,
yet also the sundown of the old man's heart,
for the shadows of grief clouded his very reason.
The funeral over, the saddened group left the graveside.
It was when the gravediggers started their task
that strange things began to take place.
Fifteen to four.
Yup, right on schedule. There's the
ol' San Fernando Valley
out there now.
-You better radio in
for landing instructions, Danny.
-Right, Jeff.
Burbank Tower, this is American
Flight 812, over.
Wouldn't surprise
me any if  he's asleep this time of the morning.
American Flight 812, this is Burbank Tower.
If I were asleep
you'd never get on the ground!
Your case maybe you'd be up there for good. Over.
You got me that time, Mac.
This American Flight 812 requesting -
Burbank Tower to American Flight 812, over.
Holy mackeral.
-Burbank Tower to American Flight 812,
are you in trouble?
-Trouble ?
-Take a look for yourself.
-What in the world...
-That's nothing from this world.
Burbank Tower to American Flight 812,
are you in trouble? Are you in trouble?
-Mayday, mayday. Stand by, Burbank Tower.
-Do you suppose the passengers saw it?
I doubt it. Most of them are asleep.
But it was quite a jolt, Jeff. I'll check.
Good. We'll get them ready for landing.
Keep it quiet until we get instructions.
-Right.
-American Flight 812 reporting to Burbank Tower, over.
(buzzing noise)
-D'you hear anything ?
-I thought I did.
Don't like hearin' noises.
'Specially when there ain't s'posed to be any.
-Yeah, sorta spooky-like.
-Maybe we're getting' old.
-Whatever it is it's gone now.
-That's the best thing for us too. Gone.
-Yeah, let's go.
(The two men scream.)
The grief of his wife's death
became greater and greater agony.
The home they had so long shared together,
became a tomb.
A sweet memory of her joyous living.
The sky to which she had once looked,
was now only a covering for her dead body.
The ever-beautiful flowers she had
planted with her own hands,
became nothing more than the
lost roses of her cheeks.
Confused by his great loss, the old man
left that home,
never to return again.
(tires screeching; the man cries out in pain)
(ambulance horn)
At the funeral of the old man,
unknown to his mourners,
his dead wife was watching.
-First his wife, then he.
-Tragic.
-Tell me something. Why was his wife buried in the ground,
and
he sealed in a crypt?
-Something to do with family tradition.
A superstition of some sort.
Well, it's getting' dark. Let's be on our way.
Then, as two of his mourners left his final resting place…
(screams) Look!
Minutes later, the police, led by Inspector Daniel Clay,
arrived at the scene.
-Who found him ?
-The man and girl.
-Medical, uh, examiner been 'round yet?
-Just left.
The morgue wagon oughta be along most any time.
-You get their
statement ?
Yeah, much as we could. They're pretty scared.
-Finding a mess like this oughta make anyone frightened.
Have one of the boys take the guy
and the girl back to town. You take charge.
-Okay Inspector. What're you gonna do?
-Look around a little.
-Pretty dark out there.
Once you get beyond the range of those lights you won't be
able to see your hand in front of your face.
-I will get one of the flashlights from the patrol car.
-You be careful Clay.
-I'm a big boy now, Johnny.
Looks like a bobcat tore into them.
Yeah.
Say Lieutenant,
d'you get that funny odour ?
-How could I miss it ?
Oh, that'll be the morgue wagon now.
-That's the fifth siren in the last hour.
-Oh, something's happened down at
the cemetery. A lot of police cars and lights.
I stopped but I didn't see anything.
Oh well, whatever it is, the morning paper
will carry the whole story.
You seem to still be up there somewhere.
Maybe I am.
I don't think I've ever seen you
in this mood before.
I guess it's because I've never been
Something about your flight ?
Yeah.
What happened, Jeff ?
-I saw a flying saucer.
-A saucer?
You mean the kind from up there?
-Yeah, or its counterpart.
It was shaped like a huge cigar.
Dan either saw it too.
When it passed over, the whole compartment
lighted up with a blinding glare.
Then there was a tremendous wind that practically
knocked us off our course.
-Well did you report it?
-Yeah, I radioed in immediately and they said well
keep it quiet until you land.
Then as soon as we landed, big army brass grabbed us
and made us swear to
secrecy about the whole thing.
Oh, it burns me up. These things have been seen for years.
They're here, it's a fact.
And the public oughta know about it.
-There must be something more you can do about it.
Oh no there isn't.
Oh, but what's the use of making a fuss.
But last night I saw a flying object that
couldn't possibly have been from this planet.
But I can't say a word. I'm muzzled by army brass!
I can't even admit I saw the thing!
(loud whooshing noise)
(another whooshing noise)
(door creaks open)
Sounds like Clay's in trouble.
(Gun is empty.)
(Clay screams and chokes.)
Bet that apparition we saw had
something to do with it.
Come on.
-Is he dead ?
-Yeah.
He's messed up as bad as those two back there.
S'pose that saucer or whatever it was
had something to do with this?
Your guess is as good as mine, Larry.
But one thing's sure. Inspector Clay is dead...
murdered...and somebody's responsible!
You're in charge now, Lieutenant.
-Yeah, guess I am. Kelton.
-Yes Sir ?
Get back up to the car and get on the radio.
Tell the coroner he's gotta make another trip out here.
Well how 'bout the lab boys ?
Well who do you think we left back at the car,
boy scouts ? Come on, Larry.
Greater love hath no man, than to
lay down his life for another.
It is always difficult to have last words
over the grave of a friend.
And Inspector Daniel Clay was a friend.
A dear friend to me and to all of us.
The bell has rung upon his great career.
Now we lay him to rest. A rest well deserved, but so premature.
People turning south from the freeway
were startled when they saw
three flying saucers high over Hollywood Boulevard.
A woman, startled by the sight in the
sky, telephones the police.
There comes a time in each man's life,
when he can't even believe his own eyes.
Saucers seen over Hollywood!
Flying saucers seen over Washington D.C.
The army convoy moved into the field.
Rockets were quickly set up.
Colonel Tom Edwards, in charge of saucer field activities,
was to make the greatest decision of his career.
He made that decision. Colonel Edwards gave the signal to fire.
Then as swiftly as they had come,
they were gone.
Even to the piercing eye of radar and the speeding jet fighters.
-Quite a sight, wasn't it Sir.
-A sight I'd rather not be seeing.
-Are you worried about them Sir ?
Well, they must have a reason for their visits.
Visits? Well that would indicate visitors!
Are big guns the usual way of welcoming visitors?
We haven't always fired at them.
For a time we tried to contact them by radio, but no response.
Then they attacked a town. A small town, I'll admit.
But nevertheless a town of people.
People who died.
-I never heard about that Sir.
Well, it was covered up by the higher echelon. Take any fire,
any earthquake, any major disaster,
then wonder.
Flying saucers, Captain,
are still a rumour.
Officially.
Looks like we beat them off again Sir.
What do they want...where are they from...where are they going...
They, Sir ? Who ?
Oh, this is a training maneuver, Sir.
We only did a little practice firing at the clouds.
Yeah. I wonder what their next move will be.
What will their next move be?
Your space commander has returned from Earth.
Send him in.
You have your report?
We had to pull in here to
Space Station 7 for regeneration.
We're returning to the planet Earth
immediately thereafter.
-What progress has been made?
-We contacted government officials.
They refuse over existence.
What plan will you follow now?
Plan 9. It's been absolutely impossible to work through these Earth creatures.
Their soul is too controlled.
Plan 9...ah yes. Plan 9 deals
with the resurrection of the dead.
Long-distance electrodes shot into the pinion
pituitary glands of recent dead.
Have you attempted any of this plan as yet ?
-Yes Excellency.
How successful has it been ?
We have risen two so far.
We shall be just as successful on more.
The living...they have no suspicion of your movements ?
We had to dispose of one policeman.
However, none of those risen have been seen.
At least, not by anyone who still remains alive.
It's too bad it must be handled this way. But it must.
Those who we take from the grave will lead the way for our other operations.
Yes, Excellency.
-Continue on. Report to me
in two Earth days.
I feared His Excellency wouldn't take our report this well.
Well had he been dealing with our own people
his reaction would have been completely different.
He understands the difficulties of the Earth race.
What do you think will be the next obstacle
the Earth people will put in our way?
Well, as long as they can think we'll have our problems.
But those whom we're using cannot think. They are the dead.
Brought to a simulated life by our electrode guns.
You know, it's an interesting thing when you consider...the Earth people, who can think,
are so frightened by those who cannot: the dead.
Well our ship should be regenerated. We better get started.
I still think you oughta go in town and stay with your mother until I get back.
This is our home and nothing's going to take me from it.
Besides, most men try and keep their wives from going home to Momma.
-That's not the point.
-That's all the point there's going to be.
Now toddle off and fly your flying machine, Darling.
But if you see any more
flying saucers, will you tell them to pick another house to buzz?
Be careful. Don't worry about me.
Oh you're the only thing I do worry about. Oh forget about the flying saucers.
They're up there. But there's something in that cemetery,
and that's too close for comfort.
The saucers are up there. And the cemetery's out there.
But I'll be locked up in there. Now off to your wild blue yonders.
You promise you'll lock the doors immediately ?
I promise. Besides, I'll be in bed before half an hour is gone,
with your pillow beside me.
-My pillow ?
Well, I have to have something to keep me company while you're away.
Sometimes in the night when it does get a little lonely,
I reach over and touch it, then it doesn't seem so lonely anymore.
A crazy kid.
Well I do love you, Darlin'.
See you Thursday.
-Goodbye, Honey.
You know I'm not leaving here until you're locked safely inside.
All right, Darling.
If you're especially nice I may even lock the side door.
And be sure you keep the yard lights on.
You're mighty silent this trip, Jeff.
You haven't spoken ten words since takeoff.
I guess I'm preoccupied, Danny.
We've got thirty-three passengers back there that have time to be preoccupied.
Flying this flybird doesn't give you that opportunity.
I guess you're right, Danny.
-Paula ?
-Yeah.
-There's nothing wrong between you two ?
-Oh no, nothing like that.
Just that I'm worried, she being there alone and those strange things flying over the house and
those incidents in the graveyard these past few days. It's just got me worried.
Well, maybe they haven't figured out those crazy skybirds yet, but
I give you 50:1 odds
the police have figured out that cemetery thing by now.
-I hope so.
-If you're really that worried Jeff why don't you radio in and find out?
Mac should be on duty at the field by now.
He could call Paula and relay the message to you.
-Hi Edith.
-Hi Silents. I haven't heard a word from this end of the plane since we left the field.
Jeff's been giving me and himself a study in silence.
-You boys aren't feudin'?
-Oh no Edie, nothing like that.
Hey Edie, how about you and me balling it up in Albuquerque ?
Albuquerque ? Have you read that flight schedule Boy ?
-What about it ?
We land in Albuquerque at 4 am. That's strictly a nine o'clock town.
Well I know a friend that'll help us --
-Let's have a problem first, huh Danny?
-Ah he's worried about Paula.
I read about that cemetery business.
I tried to get you kids not to buy too near one of those things.
We'll get there soon enough as it is!
He thought it'd be quiet and peaceful there.
No doubt about that.
It's quiet alright, like a tomb.
I'm sorry Jeff, that was a bad joke.
Say, I almost forgot what I came in here for.
How's the coffee situation?
-Mmmm that's for me.
-That sure wouldn't hurt anything, Edie.
Okay, I'll be right back. And say Jeff, make that call to Mac.
Huh, not only will she throw water on my Albuquerque plan but now she's
repeating herself.
-How 'bout that Albuquerque ball?
-I can't resist your charm, Danny Boy.
Residents near the cemetery paid little attention to the blast of thunder
and the flash of lightning.
But from the blast, arose the moving figure of the dead old man.
(telephone rings)
Hello? Who?
Mac? Well, hi Mac!
Sure I'm all right.
I just fell asleep.
Tell Jeff I'm all right.
Okay Mac. Thanks for calling. Goodnight.
(she screams)
Mrs. Trent! Mrs. Trent! What's wrong?
(police siren)
They'll be at the hatch in a moment.
You can open it now, Tanna.
Turn off the electrodes quickly.
They can't tell us from anyone else.
It's tough to find something when you don't know what you're looking for.
-I don't think the Lieutenant does either.
-Then what're doing out here? I was off duty an hour ago.
Ah don't ask me any questions. I'm just a hard hat just like you.
What do you suppose that noise was?
Whatever it was it's no more strange than the other things happening around this cemetery.
Spirits like Old Farmer Caulder talked about.
-Heh. Maybe.
-The only spirits he saw tonight were those I smelled on his breath.
Well don't forget Mrs. Trent claims to have seen them too.
She didn't have anything on her breath.
-She was hysterical.
-Well true, she was frightened, and in a state of shock.
But, don't forget that torn nightgown and the scratched feet.
Yeah I hadn't thought of that.
I guess that's why you're a detective lieutenant
and I'm still a uniformed cop.
Sometimes it's only the breaks, Larry. In the meantime let's get-
-Lieutenant, Lieutenant! Did you hear that?
-How could we help it?
-It sure was strange.
-Know what it was?
-No more than you do.
-If it weren't for orders I'd get out of here right now.
-It was a saucer.
-A flying saucer? What makes you say that?
You remember the noise we heard the other night?
We were knocked to the ground, how could I forget?
Exactly, but you're not remembering that sound.
There you're wrong, Lieutenant.
I'm with the fact the sound is similar, but what about the blinding light?
Well haven't you heard?
Many times a saucer hasn't had a glow,
or a light of any kind for that matter.
-That proves it. What next Lieutenant?
Oh, Lieutenant! Maybe this doesn't mean much,
but uh Jamie and me found a grave that looks like it's been busted into.